A Guide to the David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1992-1996, RG 44 FA253
Rockefeller Archive Center
- David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1992-1996, 44; 54.6 Cubic Feet 42 standard record storage boxes.
  - Welfare, 1992-1996; 32
    - Welfare - A-Z (Box 111, Folder 3-5)
    - Citymeals-On-Wheels (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - The Hope Program (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - United Service Organization (USO) - A-Z (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Visiting Nurse Service of New York (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - We Can (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Animals - A-Z (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Blind - A-Z (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Blind - The Foundation Fighting Blindness (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Community Centers - A-Z (Box 112, Folder 7-8)
    - Community Centers - Union Settlement Association (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Crime Prevention - A-Z (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Day Nurseries - A-Z (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Family Counseling - A-Z (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Handicapped - A-Z (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Handicapped - The Dole Foundation (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Handicapped - ICD - International Center for the Disabled (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Handicapped - Just One Break, Inc. (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Homes - A-Z (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - (Native American) Indians - A-Z (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Legal - A-Z (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Legal - Legal Aid Society (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Legal - Pacific Legal Foundation (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Musicians - A-Z (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Orphans - A-Z (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - United Funds - A-Z (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Women, 1992-1996; 33
    - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Women - A-Z (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Youth, 1992-1996; 34
    - Youth - A-C (Box 114, Folder 12-13)
    - Youth - D-Z (Box 115, Folder 1-3)
    - Boy Scouts of America - A-Z (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Greater New York Councils (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs of America (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Child Care Action Campaign (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Children's Aid Society (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Covenant House (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Girl Scouts of America - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Junior Achievement of New York (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Madison Square Boys and Girls Club (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Hugh O'Brien Youth Foundation (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Jackie Robinson Foundation (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Save the Children (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - YMCA (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - YWCA (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Camps - Boys Harbor (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Camps - Fresh Air Fund (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - X-Z, 1992-1996; 35
    - X, Y - Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Z - Miscellaneous (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Audiovisual materials, 1992-1996; 36
    - Arts - Museums - Intrepid Museum Foundation - The 1993 Salute to Freedom Benefit Dinner, 1993 September 23; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 12115)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - "CPC at 20: Making it Work", The Community Preservation Corporation, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 12116)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Varied Directions International - Bidu Sayao Selects, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 12117)